A Guide to the Warren Strother Collection, 1964-1992
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Warren Strother Collection, 1964-1992
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University, Blacksburg, Va.
Ms2004-005
11.5 cu. ft. 23 boxes
Collection contains official correspondence between Dr. T. Marshall Hahn and various Virginia Polytechnic Institute departments, 319 oral history interviews on cassette tapes, and 48 transcribed interviews. These materials focus on Dr. Hahn’s administration of VPI and were used to create a book entitled From VPI to State University: President T. Marshall Hahn, Jr. and the Transformation of Virginia Tech, 1962-1974 written by Warren Strother and Peter Wallenstein.
Strother, Warren, d.2006
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research with the exception of tapes and transcripts that do not have signed release forms. Restricted tapes and transcripts include interviews with Willis Anderson, Ken Baker, Bush Bannister, Harold Baumes, Jimmy Beck, Wilson Bell, Fitzgerald Bemiss, Joseph Blackburn, Wrren Brandt, J. Gordon Brown, Cliff Cutchins, James Dean, Edward Evans, T. Marshall and Peggy Hahn, Martha Harder, Albertis Harrison, William Harrison, Bob Heterick, David Hill, George Litton, Leslie Malpass, Mac McEver, Bill Matthews, Bob Pamplin, Bill Parkerson, Bob Paterson, Bob Pusey, Roy Smith, Paul Torgersen, Jim Tucker, Wendell Wisend, Bob Willey, Coyt Wilson, and Charlie Yates
Acquisition Information
The Warren Strother Collection was donated to Special Collections in 2004.
Biographical Note
In 1964, Warren H. Strother was hired as Virginia Tech's Director of Public Relations, which included supervising The Techgram, a student newspaper. Before this, Mr. Strother worked at the Richmond Times-Dispatch, a newspaper in Richmond, Virginia. In 1965, Strother was named Director of the Division of Information Services at Virginia Tech. Before his retirement in 1974, Strother also served as the faculty advisor for WUVT, a student radio station at Virginia Tech. He died in 2006.
Scope and Content
The collection contains materials generated from 1964 to 1994 and is organized into three series. The first series spans from 1964-1974 and consists of official correspondence from Dr. Hahn's administration. These materials include information regarding students' academic progress, organizations, and unrest during the Vietnam War; faculty activities, Board of Visitors meetings; Virginia Polytechnic Institute's legal name change to Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University; budgetary and funding information; various academic departments; and Radford College.
The materials in the second series covers 1988-1994 and consists of transcribed interviews with Willis Anderson, Ken Baker, Bush Bannister, Charles Burchard, Harold Baumes, Jimmy Beck, Wilson Bell, Fitzgerald Bemiss, Joseph Blackburn, Warren Brandt, J. Gordon Brown, Tom Cook, Cliff Cutchins, James Dean, Edward Evans, Charlie Engel, Charlie Gordon, T. Marshall Hahn, Peggy Hahn, Dana Hamel, Martha Harder, Albertis Harrison, Jr., William Harrison, Bob Heterick, David Hill, George Litton, Leslie Malpass, Mac McEver, Bill Mitchell, Ed and Peggy Moore, Bob Pamplin, Bill Parkerson, Bob Paterson, Bob Pusey, Randall Robertson, Bill Skelton, Roy Smith, Paul Torgersen, Jim Tucker, Wendell Wisend, Coyt Wilson, and Charlie Yates.
The third series also covers 1988-1994 and consists of recorded interviews on cassette tapes with Carl Allen, Willis Anderson, Lee Arp, Charlie Aull, Ken Baker, Bush Bannister, Jack Bates, Harold Baumes, Jimmy Beck, Wilson Bell, Fitzgerald Bemiss, Joseph Blackburn, Neil Boyd, Warren Brandt, J. Gordon Brown, Charles Burchard, Mel Carico, Ron Carrier, Catherine Cassell, Bill Cato, Frank Clement, Tom Cook, Weldon Cooper, Al Crawford, Cliff Cutchins, Gordon Davies, James Dean, Charlie Engel, Edward Evans, Bill Flowers, Dick Gillis, Tom Gilmer, Governor Goodwin, Charlie Gordon, George Gray, Jim Grayson, T. Marshall Hahn, Peggy Hahn, Dana Hamel, Guy Hammond, Jack Hancock, Martha Harder, Laura Jane Harper, Albertis Harrison, Jr., William Harrison, Boyd Harshbarger, William Havard, Sandy Hawthorne, David Henderson, Karl Hereford, Bob Heterick, David Hill, Dick Holmquiest, Guy Hommono, Bill Hopkins, John Hosner, J. Jones, Chuck Kennedy, Stan Kingma, Lyle Kinnear, Wybe Kroontje, L. Kuhn, W. Lavery, George Long, Carter Lowance, Wally Lowry, Leslie Malpass, Esther Martin, Jim Martin, Howard Massey, Bill Matthews, Mac McEver, Bill McFarlane, Dan Michelson, Wayne Michie, Bill Mitchell, Les Molfron, Jim Montgomery, Ed and Peggy Moore, Mark Musick, Jim Nichols, Mark Oliver, Phil Oliver, Bob Pamplin, William Parkerson, Pat Paschall, Bob Paterson, Dan Pletta, Howard Price, Bob Pusey, Sol Rawles, Tom Rice, Bud Robertson, Randall Robertson, Andy Robeson, John Rocovich, David Ross, Buddy Russell, Rusty Ryland, Lon Savage, Charles Schiffert, Edger Shannon, Bill Skelton, Roy Smith, ray Smoot, Wilson Snipes, Bill Sterrett, Dick Talbot, Paul Torgersen, Jim Tucker, Wendell Weisend, Bill White, Jim Wiggert, Jane Wilhelm, Erwin Will, BobWilley, Coyt Wilson, Wyatt Wilson, and Charlie Yates.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged alphabetically in the following series: Series 1 consists of subject folders and includes mainly correspondence from 1964-1974.
Series 2 contains transcripts of the interview cassette tapes. These interviews were conducted between 1988 and 1992.
Series 3 consists of interview cassette tapes.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Virginia Polytechnic Institute; Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
Local Subjects:
University Archives
Contents List
- Series I: Subject Files.
  - Affirmative Action. (Box-folder 1-1)
  - Agriculture. (Box-folder 1-2)
  - Agricultural Extension. (Box-folder 1-3)
  - Alumni. (Box-folder 1-4)
  - American Association of University Professors (AAUP). (Box-folder 1-5)
  - Animal Treatment. (Box-folder 1-6)
  - Annual Report, Technical Services. (Box-folder 1-7)
  - Appropriation. (Box-folder 1-8)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of. (Box-folder 1-9)
  - Athletics. (Box-folder 1-10)
  - Audio-Visuals Committee and Television Task Force. (Box-folder 1-11)
  - Bicycle Pedestrian Accidents. (Box-folder 1-12)
  - Blacksburg Bypass. (Box-folder 1-13)
  - Board of Visitors, 1964. (Box-folder 1-14)
  - Board of Visitors, 1968-1969. (Box-folder 1-15)
  - Board of Visitors, 1970-1971. (Box-folder 1-16)
  - Board of Visitors, 1972. (Box-folder 1-17)
  - Board of Visitors, 1973. (Box-folder 1-18)
  - Brandt, Warren. (Box-folder 2-1)
  - Budget Advisory Board. (Box-folder 2-2)
  - Burchard, Charles. (Box-folder 2-3)
  - Capital Outlay Requests. (Box-folder 2-4)
  - Civil Rights. (Box-folder 2-5)
  - College Enrollment Increase. (Box-folder 2-6)
  - Commission on Undergraduate Student Affairs. (Box-folder 2-7)
  - Co-operative Students. (Box-folder 2-8)
  - Corps of Cadets. (Box-folder 2-9)
  - Council of Presidents. (Box-folder 2-10)
  - Crisis Center. (Box-folder 2-11)
  - Development. (Box-folder 2-12)
  - "Dixie," Playing of and Display of Confederate Battle Flag. (Box-folder 2-13)
  - Dormitory Visitation Policy. (Box-folder 2-14)
  - Education Acts and Titles. (Box-folder 2-15)
  - Extension. (Box-folder 2-16)
  - Fabian, R. Craig. (Box-folder 2-17)
  - Faculty, 1967-1968. (Box-folder 2-18)
  - Faculty, 1969. (Box-folder 2-19)
  - Faculty, 1970. (Box-folder 2-20)
  - Faculty Consulting. (Box-folder 3-1)
  - Faculty Professional Activities. (Box-folder 3-2)
  - Faculty Senate, 1967-1968. (Box-folder 3-3)
  - Faculty Senate, 1969-1973. (Box-folder 3-4)
  - Female Faculty. (Box-folder 3-5)
  - Fraternity and Sorority Affairs, 1966-1970. (Box-folder 3-6)
  - Fraternity and Sorority Affairs, 1971. (Box-folder 3-7)
  - Fraternity and Sorority Affairs, 1972-1974. (Box-folder 3-8)
  - Funding, Raising and Development. (Box-folder 3-9)
  - Geology Equipment. (Box-folder 3-10)
  - Graduate Degrees. (Box-folder 3-11)
  - Graduate Placement. (Box-folder 3-12)
  - Graduate Programs. (Box-folder 3-13)
  - Hahn, Marshall-Disclosure of Assets. (Box-folder 3-14)
  - Hahn, Marshall-Personal. (Box-folder 3-15)
  - Harper, George M. (Box-folder 3-16)
  - Higher Education-Virginia in the 1970s. (Box-folder 3-17)
  - Higher Education-Funding. (Box-folder 3-18)
  - Lane, E. H. (Box-folder 3-19)
  - Lavery, W. E. (Box-folder 3-20)
  - Legal Concerns. (Box-folder 3-21)
  - Library. (Box-folder 3-22)
  - Management Consultants. (Box-folder 3-23)
  - Masters of Business Administration Program. (Box-folder 3-24)
  - McKeefery, William J. (Box-folder 3-25)
  - Minority Concerns. (Box-folder 4-1)
  - Music Department. (Box-folder 4-2)
  - Politics. (Box-folder 4-3)
  - President's Staff Meetings. (Box-folder 4-4)
  - Press Relations. (Box-folder 4-5)
  - Public Information Program. (Box-folder 4-6)
  - Quarterly Report, Winter 1971. (Box-folder 4-7)
  - Radford College. (Box-folder 4-8)
  - Religious Concerns. (Box-folder 4-9)
  - Research Park. (Box-folder 4-10)
  - Residual Funds. (Box-folder 4-11)
  - Ross, David. (Box-folder 4-12)
  - ROTC. (Box-folder 4-13)
  - Senate, Student Government Association. (Box-folder 4-14)
  - Shaner Report. (Box-folder 4-15)
  - Space Utilization. (Box-folder 4-16)
  - State Funding. (Box-folder 4-17)
  - State Technical Services. (Box-folder 4-18)
  - Student Concerns. (Box-folder 4-19)
  - Student Government Association. (Box-folder 4-20)
  - Student Health Services. (Box-folder 4-21)
  - Student Interns. (Box-folder 4-22)
  - Student Legislators Forum. (Box-folder 4-23)
  - Student Life. (Box-folder 4-24)
  - Student Life Policy. (Box-folder 4-25)
  - Student Unrest. (Box-folder 5-1)
  - Study Abroad. (Box-folder 5-2)
  - Summary Report on Hahn's Administration of VPI. (Box-folder 5-3)
  - Summer Interns. (Box-folder 5-4)
  - Title IX. (Box-folder 5-5)
  - University Council and Governance. (Box-folder 5-6)
  - University Finances. (Box-folder 5-7)
  - University Planning. (Box-folder 5-8)
  - Virginia Academy of Science. (Box-folder 5-9)
  - Vocational Education. (Box-folder 5-10)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute-Legal Name. (Box-folder 5-11)
  - WBRA-Television. (Box-folder 5-12)
  - Whitehurst, Capt. James L. (Box-folder 5-13)
  - YMCA. (Box-folder 5-14)
- Series II: Interview Transcripts.
  - Anderson, Willis. (Box-folder 6-1)
  - Baker, Ken. (Box-folder 6-2)
  - Bannister, Bush. (Box-folder 6-3)
  - Burchard, Charles. (Box-folder 6-4)
  - Baumes, Harold. (Box-folder 6-5)
  - Beck, Jimmy. (Box-folder 6-6)
  - Bell, Wilson, 1989. (Box-folder 6-7)
  - Bell, Wilson, 1990. (Box-folder 6-8)
  - Bemiss, Fitzgerald. (Box-folder 6-9)
  - Blackburn, Joseph. (Box-folder 6-10)
  - Brandt, Warren. (Box-folder 6-11)
  - Brown, J. Gordon. (Box-folder 6-12)
  - Cook, Tom. (Box-folder 6-13)
  - Cutchins, Cliff. (Box-folder 6-14)
  - Dean, James W. (Box-folder 6-15)
  - Evans, Edward B. (Box-folder 6-16)
  - Engel, Charlie. (Box-folder 6-17)
  - Gordon, Charlie. (Box-folder 6-18)
  - Hahn, Jr., T. Marshall and Peggy, 5/1989-11/1989.. (Box-folder 6-19)
  - Hahn Biography. (Box-folder 7-1)
  - Hamel, Dana-Interview 1. (Box-folder 7-2)
  - Hamel, Dana-Interview 2. (Box-folder 7-3)
  - Harder, Martha. (Box-folder 7-4)
  - Harrison, Jr., Albertis S. (Box-folder 7-5)
  - Harrison, William B. (Box-folder 7-6)
  - Heterick, Bob. (Box-folder 7-7)
  - Hill, David. (Box-folder 7-8)
  - Litton, George. (Box-folder 7-9)
  - Malpass, Leslie. (Box-folder 7-10)
  - Matthews, Bill. (Box-folder 7-11)
  - McEver, Mac. (Box-folder 7-12)
  - Mitchell, Bill, 1989. (Box-folder 7-13)
  - Moore, Ed and Peggy. (Box-folder 7-14)
  - Pamplin, Robert. (Box-folder 7-15)
  - Parkerson, William F. (Box-folder 7-16)
  - Paterson, Bob. (Box-folder 7-17)
  - Pusey, Bob. (Box-folder 7-18)
  - Robertson, Randall. (Box-folder 7-19)
  - Skelton, Bill, Part I. (Box-folder 7-20)
  - Skelton, Bill, Part II. (Box-folder 7-21)
  - Smith, Roy. (Box-folder 7-22)
  - Torgerson, Paul, Part I. (Box-folder 8-1)
  - Torgerson, Paul, Part II. (Box-folder 8-2)
  - Tucker, Jim. (Box-folder 8-3)
  - Weisend, Wendy. (Box-folder 8-4)
  - Willey, Bob. (Box-folder 8-5)
  - Wilson, Coyt. (Box-folder 8-6)
  - Yates, Charlie. (Box-folder 8-7)
- Series III: Interview Cassette Tapes.
  - Allen, Martin, Greg, and Lowry, 6/6/89. (Box 9)
  - Anderson, Wick (2 tapes), 2/10/89. (Box 9)
  - Arp, Lee (2 tapes), 9/19/89. (Box 9)
  - Aull, Charlie (2 tapes), 3/26/90. (Box 9)
  - Baker, Ken (2 tapes), 7/6/89. (Box 9)
  - Bannister, Bush (2 tapes), 6/7/89. (Box 9)
  - Bates, Jack (2 tapes), 11/20/90. (Box 9)
  - Baumer, Harold and Bill Parkerson. (Box 9)
  - Beck, Jimmy (2 tapes), 3/21/89. (Box 9)
  - Beck, Jimmy and Bob Pusey (2 tapes), 12/27/90. (Box 9)
  - Bell, Wilson (2 tapes), 2/6/89. (Box 9)
  - Bell, Wilson (10 tapes), 3/18/89. (Box 9)
  - Bell, Wilson (3 tapes), 1/16/90. (Box 9)
  - Bemiss, Fitzgerald (2 tapes), 3/20/89. (Box 9)
  - Blackburn, Joe, 3/21/89. (Box 9)
  - Blackburn, Joe (2 tapes), 3/21/89. (Box 10)
  - Blackburn, Joe, 11/19/90. (Box 10)
  - Boyd, Neil (2 tapes), 2/16/90. (Box 10)
  - Brandt, Warren (6 tapes), 8/25/89. (Box 10)
  - Brown, Gordon (3 tapes), 6/28/89. (Box 10)
  - Burchard, Charles (2 tapes), 6/19/89. (Box 10)
  - Carico, Mel and Bill Hopkins, 5/2/89. (Box 10)
  - Carrier, Ron (2 tapes), 3/21/90. (Box 10)
  - Cassell, Catherine (2 tapes), 8/30/89. (Box 10)
  - Cato, Bill (2 tapes), 6/13/92. (Box 10)
  - Clement, Frank (2 tapes), 2/10/89. (Box 10)
  - Cook, Tom (2 tapes), 10/30/89. (Box 10)
  - Cooper, Weldon and George Long (2 tapes), 5/23/89. (Box 10)
  - Crawford, Al (3 tapes), 6/4/90. (Box 10)
  - Culden, Cliff. (Box 10)
  - Cutchins, Cliff, 3/17/89. (Box 10)
  - Davies, Gordon (2 tapes), 5/29/90. (Box 10)
  - Dean, Jim (2 tapes), 6/21/89. (Box 11)
  - Engel, Charlie (3 tapes), 4/10/89. (Box 11)
  - Engel, Charlie, 12/7/94. (Box 11)
  - Evans, Ed (2 tapes), 5/29/91. (Box 11)
  - Evans, Ed and Howard Prize and Don Pletta, 7/23/91-7/24/91. (Box 11)
  - Flowers, Bill (2 tapes), 1/30/90. (Box 11)
  - Gillis, Dick (2 tapes), 7/10/89. (Box 11)
  - Gilmer, Tom (2 tapes), 1/2/89. (Box 11)
  - Godwin, Governor (6 tapes), 3/14/89. (Box 11)
  - Gordon, C. and Ray Smoot (5 tapes), 6/23/89. (Box 11)
  - Gray, George, 5/15/89. (Box 11)
  - Grayson, Jim (2 tapes), 7/11/90. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 7/1/89. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 7/8/89. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 8/5/89. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 8/31/89. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 10/7/89. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 2/10/90. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 3/24/90. (Box 11)
  - Hahn, Marshall, 4/6/91. (Box 12)
  - Hahn, Marshall (10 tapes). (Box 12)
  - Hahn, Peggy (2 tapes), 11/14/89. (Box 12)
  - Hamel, Dana (2 tapes), 3/20/89. (Box 12)
  - Hamel, Dana (3 tapes), 3/19/90. (Box 12)
  - Hamel, Dana, 3/19/90. (Box 13)
  - Hammond, Guy, 2/23/90. (Box 13)
  - Hancock, Jack, 2/10/89. (Box 13)
  - Harder, Martha (2 tapes), 5/25/89. (Box 13)
  - Harper, Laura Jane (2 tapes), 5/30/89. (Box 13)
  - Harrison, Albertus (2 tapes), 8/28/90. (Box 13)
  - Harrison, William B. (3 tapes), 4/14/92. (Box 13)
  - Harshbarger, Boyd (2 tapes), 7/6/90. (Box 13)
  - Havard, William (2 tapes), 3/31/89. (Box 13)
  - Hawthorne, Sandy (2 tapes), 7/10/90. (Box 13)
  - Henderson, David and Dan Michelson (2 tapes), 4/16/90. (Box 14)
  - Hereford, Karl (2 tapes), 8/26/89. (Box 14)
  - Heterick, Bob (4 tapes), 6/22/89. (Box 14)
  - Hill, David (2 tapes), 4/13/90. (Box 14)
  - Holmquist, Dick (2 tapes), 3/2/89. (Box 14)
  - Hopkins, Bill, 5/2/89. (Box 14)
  - Hosner, John (2 tapes), 5/18/89. (Box 14)
  - Jones, J. B., 5/24/89. (Box 14)
  - Jones, J. B. and Bill Harrison and Les Molfron, 11/12/91 & 11/25/91. (Box 15)
  - Kennedy, Chuck (3 tapes), 3/2/90. (Box 15)
  - Kingma, Stan (3 tapes), 10/18/89. (Box 15)
  - Kinnear, Lyle (2 tapes), 11/8/89. (Box 15)
  - Kroontje, Wybe (2 tapes), 3/17/89. (Box 15)
  - Kuhn, L. M. (2 tapes), 3/22/89. (Box 15)
  - Lavery, W. E. (2 tapes), 6/2/89. (Box 15)
  - Lavery, W. E., 8/27/89. (Box 15)
  - Lavery, W. E. (2 tapes), 2/13/90. (Box 15)
  - Lavery, W. E., 2/13/90. (Box 16)
  - Lavery, W. E. (2 tapes), 4/24/90. (Box 16)
  - Lowance, Carter (2 tapes), 3/15/89. (Box 16)
  - Lowry, Wally (2 tapes), 9/20/89. (Box 16)
  - Malpass, Leslie (2 tapes), 3/31/89. (Box 16)
  - Malpass, Leslie (2 tapes), 10/12/89. (Box 16)
  - Malpass, Leslie (2 tapes), 4/18/90. (Box 16)
  - Martin, Jim (5 tapes), 5/4/90. (Box 16)
  - Martin, Jim, 5/4/90. (Box 17)
  - Massey, Howard (2 tapes), 1/26/89. (Box 17)
  - Matthews, Bill (2 tapes), 2/8/89. (Box 17)
  - McEver, Mac (2 tapes), 11/16/89. (Box 17)
  - McFarlane, Bill (2 tapes), 6/6/90. (Box 17)
  - Michie, Wayne (2 tapes), 10/18/89. (Box 17)
  - Mitchell, Bill (5 tapes), 8/26/89. (Box 17)
  - Montgomery, Jim and Lon Savage (2 tapes), 7/21/89. (Box 17)
  - Moore, Ed and Peggy (3 tapes), 4/28/89. (Box 18)
  - Musick, Mark (2 tapes), 3/17/89. (Box 18)
  - Nichols, Jim (2 tapes), 6/8/90. (Box 18)
  - Oliver, Mark (2 tapes), 2/21/89. (Box 18)
  - Pamplin, Bob (2 tapes), 11/2/89. (Box 18)
  - Parkerson, Bill, 3/22/89. (Box 18)
  - Paschall, Pat (2 tapes), 3/15/89. (Box 18)
  - Paterson, Bob (2 tapes), 4/24/92. (Box 18)
  - Pletta, Dan (3 tapes), 8/15/89. (Box 18)
  - Pletta, Dan, 8/15/89. (Box 19)
  - Price, Howard and Bill Sterrett, 2/16/89. (Box 19)
  - Pusey, Bob (3 tapes), 1/29/91. (Box 19)
  - Rawles, Sol (2 tapes), 8/21/91. (Box 19)
  - Rice, Tom (4 tapes), 7/10/89. (Box 19)
  - Robertson, Bud, 5/22/89. (Box 19)
  - Robertson, Randall (2 tapes), 6/9/89. (Box 19)
  - Robeson, Andy (4 tapes), 2/15/89. (Box 19)
  - Rocovich, John (2 tapes), 10/16/89. (Box 20)
  - Ross, David (2 tapes), 3/20/90. (Box 20)
  - Russell, Buddy (2 tapes), 1/29/90. (Box 20)
  - Ryland, Rusty (2 tapes), 1/23/90. (Box 20)
  - Savage, Lon (3 tapes), 11/10/89. (Box 20)
  - Savage, Lon (3 tapes), 12/13/89. (Box 20)
  - Schiffert, Charles (2 tapes), 11/21/89. (Box 20)
  - Shannon, Edger, 5/23/89. (Box 20)
  - Shannon, Edger, 5/23/89. (Box 21)
  - Skelton, Bill (3 tapes), 12/4/89. (Box 21)
  - Skelton, Bill (3 tapes), 2/21/90. (Box 21)
  - Smith, Roy (3 tapes), 3/29/89. (Box 21)
  - Smith, Roy, 9/15/89. (Box 21)
  - Snipes, Wilson (2 tapes), 5/16/89. (Box 21)
  - Talbot, Dick (2 tapes), 5/15/89. (Box 21)
  - Telephone I (2 tapes). (Box 21)
  - Telephone II. (Box 21)
  - Torgersen, Paul (2 tapes), 8/9/89. (Box 22)
  - Torgersen, Paul (3 tapes), 6/5/90. (Box 22)
  - Tucker, Jim (2 tapes), 9/15/89. (Box 22)
  - Weisend, Wendell (2 tapes), 11/7/89. (Box 22)
  - White, Bill (2 tapes), 1/23/90. (Box 22)
  - Wiggert, Jim (2 tapes), 5/21/90. (Box 22)
  - Wilhelm, Jane (2 tapes), 11/2/90. (Box 22)
  - Will, Erwin (3 tapes), 3/23/89. (Box 22)
  - Will, Erwin (2 tapes), 3/23/89. (Box 23)
  - Willey, Bob (2 tapes), 1/30/90. (Box 23)
  - Willey, Bob and Phil Oliver (2 tapes), 10/15/90-10/16/91. (Box 23)
  - Williams, Wyatt (2 tapes), 3/13/89. (Box 23)
  - Wilson, Coyt (2 tapes), 5/17/89. (Box 23)
  - WVTF FM Radio, 5/17/89. (Box 23)
  - Yates, Charlie (2 tapes), 2/6/92. (Box 23)